THE LEGEND OF KITCHEN SOLDIER
I must be crazy. I really must be.
I still had leave left, but I just had to come crawling back.
Darn it.
But still, it's good to have you in the mess hall.
It feels full and lively, sir.
Right? I do have a pretty big presence, don't I?
You have advanced to Intermediate Cook.
Your Basic Knife Skills speed has increased by 1.5 times.
Was he always that fast with a knife?
Oh, Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun.
You can take a break. I'll be done in a flash.
All right. Wait, what?
Aren't you pushing yourself too hard?
This is nothing.
Oh, right. Could you toss me the sesame seeds?
Here!
Yes, thank you.
Impressive.
Beef bulgogi, four stars. Stir-fried anchovies, four stars.
Level up.
AVAILABLE SKILLS
New Skill available. Check Gourmet Rating.
Gourmet Rating? What's that?
Fulfill the Gourmet Rating to earn additional rewards.
So, are we ready for the guys to come in?
GOURMET RATING
This is so cool.
What, you punk? Are you laughing at your senior now?
No, sir.
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun, what's your favorite dish?
I don't eat for taste. I eat to see how much protein I'm getting.
Oh, protein is very important, sir.
You don't sound very convinced.
Hey, protein is essential for building muscle, you know.
All right. Salute.
GOURMET RATING
Kang Seong-jae, stop making the food so delicious, all right?
- I keep gaining weight because of you. - Listen to you.
You're talking like Kang Seong-jae did all the cooking.
You can tell Kang Seong-jae made this just by how good it looks, sir.
- You are acting up - Enjoy your meal, sir.
Now that I'm powerless before my discharge, right?
- Enjoy your meal, sir. - Thank you.
- You don't even answer me. - Enjoy your meal.
- Enjoy your meal. - Enjoy your meal.
Today's menu is Korean Traditional Style One, Two, Three, Four, and Five.
GOURMET RATING
You could've just said home-style Korean meal. Why make it sound so complicated?
Home-style Korean meal. Oh, so you understood?
The very nature of a dish changes depending on the name it's given.
Yes, sure.
What would someone who only eats tofu and kimchi know about it?
Jeez, you think I eat it because I want to?
I'd eat better stuff if we had it. I eat it because there's nothing else.
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae, you got something to say?
- No, sir. Enjoy your meal. - How silly.
What a jerk.
GOURMET RATING
What are you staring at? Where's my soup?
Private First Class Tak Mun-ik, I didn't realize you were so picky.
Hey, TMI.
Were you being sassy and complaining about the food?
Would a worthless Private First Class like myself dare do such a thing, sir?
I should just be grateful for whatever I'm served.
Right.
The stir-fried anchovies are well-cooked and not too sticky.
The beef bulgogi isn't overdone, so it's still tender and juicy.
And the seasoning is perfect, sir.
You have fulfilled the Gourmet Rating for all the Ganglim Outpost Soldiers.
You have earned bonus Experience Points.
INTERMEDIATE COOK
It's true that lately
Even when I complete a Quest, my Experience Points
Don't increase like they used to.
The higher the grade of the dish you complete
The more Experience Points you can acquire.
Higher grade?
Oh, now that I think about it I've never made a five-star dish before.
EARN MORE EXPERIENCE POINTS BY COMPLETING HIGHER-GRADE DISHES
EPISODE 9
Frozen yellow croaker. Grade C from Jeju Island.
Grade C?
Can I make a five-star dish with this?
Whatever, let's just do it.
FRIED YELLOW CROAKER: SPRINKLE A SMALL AMOUNT
OF SALT, COOKING WINE, AND LEMON JUICE
Hero, the oil is hot enough.
What are you up to again?
- Just finish it. - Yes, sir.
TERRIFYING MINESWEEPER
RESPECTED BATTALION COMMANDER
- Salute! Yes, Battalion Commander. - Seok-ho, have you had lunch?
Yes, I have. Have you eaten, Battalion Commander?
I always make sure to eat well.
From the sound of your voice, Seok-ho, you sound
Completely out of energy, as if you skipped lunch.
Oh, that's not it.
Come on, I can tell just by the sound of your voice.
It's plain as day that you're sulking because Min-gu got promoted.
Is that so? I'm really fine.
Min-gu might have gotten a bit of a head start
But no one knows who will reach the finish line first, you know?
I'll make sure to back you up during the next promotion review
So don't worry.
Battalion Commander, your words alone are more than enough. Thank you.
Anyway, to congratulate the guys getting promoted
The Regimental Commander wants everyone to gather at the Officers' Mess.
- The Company Commander has to be there. - Well, if you're inviting me
I'll definitely be there.
The Ganglim men went through a lot because of the typhoon.
Bring the Outpost Commander and Private First Class Kang Seong-jae with you.
But why Private First Class Kang Seong-jae?
I just keep getting cravings for his cooking.
And it seems the Regimental Commander is curious too.
Battalion Commander.
I, Hwang Seok-ho, will prepare thoroughly and be there.
Right.
Hwang Seok-ho, let's get that promotion!
MAINTAIN ORDER IN THE SERVING LINE
Why are you doing all that to a yellow croaker?
You can just coat it in oil and fry it.
Isn't that how you made the dish
That we couldn't tell if it was a croaker or a goby?
What is this?
Just eat it. Next.
Private First Class Tak Mun-ik!
FRIED YELLOW CROAKER
If I do this...
It will be the perfectly fried yellow croaker.
WELL-COOKED FRIED YELLOW CROAKER
BUT NOT 5-STAR
Well...
This isn't it.
Why? It looks delicious. I'll try it.
WELL-COOKED FRIED YELLOW CROAKER BUT NOT 5-STAR
This sauce is insane! It's delicious.
What am I missing? My gosh.
I'm not just saying that. It's really delicious.
So what are you so unhappy about?
I don't know what the problem is.
I mean, I need to know what the problem is
So that I, Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun can decide whether or not to help you.
There's this thing...
- Geez. - Hey. What's with the sigh?
So, I guess someone like me is no help to you now, right?
You sucked up all my know-how
During my final year of service, and now you don't need me?
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun.
If the food I make is, say, four stars
I feel like it's missing that one thing to make it five.
But I just don't know what that is.
Now you're talking like some kind of food critic?
Hey, four stars, five stars... That's just you being greedy.
It's not like we have a bunch of foodies around here.
That kind of perfect food? That's for
Somewhere like the Officers' Mess. They're not going to eat just anything.
- You mean the Officers' Mess? - Yes, the Officers' Mess.
The Battalion Commander specifically requested that I bring
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae to the Officers' Mess.
The Officers' Mess is already full of soldiers who are great cooks
So why does he specifically want to eat Seong-jae's food?
Come on, how can a person live on nothing but fine dining?
I'm sure the Battalion Commander wants
To hit up a snack bar every once in a while, too.
This is to celebrate the Battalion Commander's promotion.
And as a Company Commander, shouldn't I at least grant him this one request?
I'm just not sure it's appropriate for me to attend such an important event.
He specifically told me to bring you along, Ye-rin.
Our Battalion Commander...
He can be a bit scary when he's serious but he's a truly warm-hearted person.
My goodness.
Is our Private First Class Kang Seong-jae already wondering
What dishes he should make?
- Well, it's just... - Now, hold on.
We can't actually serve the Battalion Commander snack food.
It should be something a little luxurious, something.
A menu that makes him feel like he's being treated to something special.
How should I put it? Something like...
Like Korean royal cuisine.
Korean royal cuisine, all of a sudden?
Why? How about sinseollo?
Sinseollo, sir?
Oh, does that have perilla powder in it too?
Company Commander, don't you think overdoing it like that
Will just make things worse?
Okay. Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
Make sure to come up with a good idea.
Got it?
GANGLIM OUTPOST
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae, are you ready?
- You mean right now, sir? - Yes, come on, let's hurry.
The Battalion Commander is waiting. Now, let's get it!
ROSE-KNIFE
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun, I'm heading out.
Salute!
Yes, Salute.
Then who's going to make lunch and do the dishes?
My gosh. Don't go!
Oh, right.
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae, sir.
Are you ready to serve a perfect meal to everyone in here?
Since you believe in me I'll do my absolute best.
Let's show them Ganglim is a force to be reckoned with.
HOGUK HALL
Hero.
A new map has been unlocked.
STAGE: OFFICERS' MESS
The Officers' Mess.
Welcome to the Officers' Mess.
STRONG WILL, WE ARE ONE! 29TH DIVISION, 1ST BATTALION
- Congratulations on your promotion. - Congratulations!
Salute!
Captain Hwang Seok-ho, 4th Company Commander.
Seok-ho, Ye-rin, you're here.
If the Battalion Commander calls for me I'll be there, no matter where, sir.
My sincerest congratulations on your promotion.
This is all thanks to you for following my lead
And helping me out, isn't it?
Oh, the Regimental Commander said he was curious
So I brought Private First Class Kang Seong-jae with me.
Good.
I hear the soldiers at Ganglim Outpost
Have been gaining a lot of weight because of him.
That braised boneless pollock you made
Had a completely unexpected flavor.
- Nice. - Thank you.
I knew you'd be like this.
So, for the distinguished guests here
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae
Will showcase his cooking.
- Oh, really? - Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
It's an honor to be invited to such a special occasion.
On the contrary, having you congratulate me
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae, I'm so flattered.
GOURMET RATING
Five stars.
Complete a five-star dish for the Regimental Commander.
Why?
- Sir? - Is there a fly on my head?
No, that's not it, sir.
It's just that I sense the powerful aura
Of a true gourmet from you, Regimental Commander.
Gosh, this kid is a great judge of character.
The Regimental Commander is very particular about his food.
I mean, he even keeps a whole list of great restaurants on his phone.
My wife is always nagging me to eat whatever
But if you're going to eat something, it might as well be delicious, right?
- Right. - That's right.
A man doing such important work should only eat the best, shouldn't he?
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae, let's show him a delicious dish
That's perfect for the Regimental Commander's
Refined and noble palate.
Yes, I'll get right on it.
Hey, someone show this man to the kitchen.
Yes, sir. I'll show him the way.
- We don't have time. Let's move. - Yes, sir.
How can I help you?
Salute! Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
I'm here to assist in the kitchen.
Oh, you don't have to salute. We're informal here.
Oh, okay.
I was told to make a dish to celebrate the promotion.
But what should I do? We weren't told anything about this.
Let me check on that. Follow me.
Corporal Lee Ho-yeong.
This guy says he's from Ganglim Outpost
And that the Battalion Commander ordered him to cook.
We have more than enough people here. Why bring in someone from Ganglim?
That's what I'm saying.
GOURMET RATING
Gourmet Rating cannot be verified.
Why are you staring at me like that?
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae, 4th Company, Ganglim Outpost.
I look forward to working with you.
Outpost? I don't think a cook from an outpost can do anything here.
We already have a full course menu planned
So I don't think we can just give you something to do all of a sudden.
Well, then... I'll make a dish that I'm capable of.
And if you do? When are you planning to serve it?
- Pardon? - The dining sequence is part of the meal
And we can't have your dish interrupting the flow.
But still
If I make it delicious, shouldn't that be enough?
Oh, is that right?
You can cook over there.
As for ingredients, open the fridge and grab whatever you need.
Yes, I understand.
Hey, who brought that guy in?
They say he's from Ganglim Outpost.
Gosh, he looks like a total dud.
- This is going to be a pain. - Is the prep done?
- Not yet, sir. - Then shut your traps and finish it.
- Do we have enough time? - No, sir.
If you're done chaming the perilla leaves, get the gastrique ready.
- Yes, sir. - Chaming? Prep...
What's a gastrique?
Prep, gastrique. New keywords have been registered.
I have to pull off a five-star dish
That I've never even attempted before.
First, I need to see what I can make with the ingredients they have.
- Oh, I'm sorry. - Darn it.
My goodness.
GRADE A ORGANIC CARROTS FROM JEJU ISLAND
Grade A organic carrots.
Grown healthily in Jeju's volcanic soil
Without pesticides or chemical fertilizers.
Gosh, even the carrots they get here are organic.
Grade A Namhae spinach. Grown in the clean sea breeze
Giving it thick leaves and a rich aroma.
My goodness.
Grade A Jeju black pork loin.
Evenly marbled with fat, making it tender, not tough.
With ingredients like these...
Okay.
I can tell how fresh it is just by the sound.
Yes!
Okay, I've got it.
It's come back to this. Braised boneless pollack.
And without Kang Seong-jae, this is a huge problem.
Hey, there.
What are you doing all alone in your final year of service?
Jeez, can't you tell?
This is my punishment for getting a bad junior.
Gosh, that Kang Seong-jae is really making things difficult for everyone.
Look who's talking.
- What are you doing in the kitchen? - What do you think?
The company administration officer said not to leave you alone
So he sent me to help out.
No, I mean, there are plenty of other guys, so why you?
Well...
Who else can put up with Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun?
They've just stuck the top two most senior guys
At the outpost in the mess hall. What a total mess.
So, what should I start prepping?
It's...
Braised boneless pollack.
What?
Braised boneless pollack without Kang Seong-jae?
How are we supposed to make it?
You have no idea how cute my daughter is.
They say parents are a mirror for their children
And she copies everything I do.
I've taken her out for so much good food
That she's become quite the picky eater.
My son just sits around playing games all day.
I have no idea who he takes after.
It drives me crazy watching him. Absolutely crazy.
But nowadays, gaming is considered a valuable skill, isn't it?
The Republic of Korea is a powerhouse in e-sports
So you never know he could become a great gamer.
That's only if he's good at it.
I don't know much about games, but from what I've seen
He's really terrible at it.
If you don't have the talent for something you should know when to quit.
But he's stubborn about the wrong things.
So, Outpost Commander, what were you like as a kid?
Well...
I think I was just an ordinary student.
You know, quiet and unremarkable.
That's surprising. I figured our Outpost Commander
Would've been quite something back in school.
The Company Commander would know, right?
How stubborn our Outpost Commander is.
Stubborn...
She is, rather. Our Outpost Commander.
Stubbornness. It's important.
But telling the difference between determination
And just being pigheaded, I think that's important too.
Our people at Ganglim are all good.
But I'm starting to see these little shortcomings one by one.
I'm only saying this because it's a shame to see.
Let's have a drink.
Salute!
This guy has a bit of main character syndrome.
I was a little late carrying out
A grave mission befitting my new rank.
And you got the job done?
Yes, of course.
Nice.
I've been working all day and haven't had a single decent meal.
Thanks, 4th Company Commander.
But you must not be very busy over there
Seeing as you got here so early.
If you stir-fry it for too long
The texture of the noodles will be ruined.
The noodles might get soggy, so be careful.
Just mix the ingredients and it's ready to go out.
Just the ingredients.
My goodness.
When the Regimental Commander dined with us before
I heard him mention he eats lotus root for his circulation
So I prepared some fried lotus root chips.
I fried thinly sliced lotus root, and topped it with beef tartare.
- Please enjoy. Salute! - Thanks.
I guess you have to be this good to be a soldier in the Officers' Mess.
This is why I can't help but adore this guy.
All right, then. At a time like this
Shouldn't we launch one of our missiles?
Regimental Commander, your timing is perfect as always.
All right, missile.
- For the future, for love, for work! - Launch!
The terrifying braised boneless pollack.
Don't you think we should at least do something?
You saw what Kang Seong-jae was doing, didn't you?
I saw it. I only watched, though.
Who knew a day like this would come again?
And that I'd have to do it alone?
Hey, that hurts. Really. You're not alone.
While you were on leave
I worked hard to get back to my old prime.
So then...
- Just the two of us? - Yes.
Shouldn't we show these kids
We didn't eat all that army food for nothing?
Right. We may not be as good as Kang Seong-jae
But we can do this.
- Yes! - Let's do this!
What? Wait a minute.
- Why? - What's wrong?
What is going on here?
Hey, where did Kang Seong-jae go? And why is that guy here?
What? Kang Seong-jae was called to the Officers' Mess.
- Darn it. This is driving me nuts. - Hey, what's on the menu today?
- Why? - It's braised boneless pollack.
I tasted it for seasoning, and it's not bad, okay?
So just take one bite
And give me your honest, truthful opinion.
The fact that Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun tasted it
Is what's really scary.
Hey! I can't take it. Let's go.
Where do you think you're going?
This is the masterpiece of Ganglim's top two cooks.
Don't complain and go eat.
I'll tell the company administration officer that you're skipping your meal.
Oh, dear.
Do you really think this makes any sense?
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun.
Get in here.
The last beef bone soup was edible
So maybe the pollack will be good too?
Corporal Joo Sang-uk.
Do you know why people fall for scams?
At first, they're really nice to you. They make you trust them.
Then the moment your suspicion fades
They take everything you have in one fell swoop.
So you're saying the beef bone soup was bait?
Of course.
Didn't I say I could do it too?
The moment you think, "Looks okay,"
And take a bite it's over.
No one stick your spoons in there carelessly.
You'll be a goner.
- Eat. - Darn it.
Whatever.
What? Oh!
I feel like they were really going for it with this one.
Hey, I'm telling you, you're being scammed.
What?
What's going on right before he's discharged?
Isn't it a bad sign when a person changes all of a sudden?
This is delicious.
It's delicious!
- Darn it. - Hey! Get it away!
We really don't get along.
KANG SEONG-JAE'S RECIPE NOTE
JAPCHAE
Japchae. Four stars.
I followed the recipe perfectly.
Let's get ready to serve the main dish!
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
If it's not a five-star dish
It won't satisfy Regimental Commander.
How can I get that final star?
At this rate, the quest will be a complete failure.
Hey.
- Are you taking that out now? - Yes. I'm about to.
- Let's take this out too. - Yes.
Wait, hold on a second.
Why? Is there something else you need to do?
Well...
It's just it feels like it's missing a little something.
Let me taste it.
It seems fine.
Should we serve it like this?
No. It's not good enough yet.
The dish we've prepared for you today
Is duck leg, marinated for 24 hours in salt and various herbs.
It was slow-cooked for three and a half hours
In 65°C duck fat to create this duck confit
Which we've paired with an orange gastrique sauce.
Please enjoy the texture of the crispy duck skin
Along with the tender meat.
Gosh, is this really the same duck dish we're used to?
On such a special day
We felt an ordinary dish wouldn't properly convey our congratulations
So we put a great deal of care into it.
Please, enjoy your meal.
Thanks!
Gosh, just the smell of this makes me feel full already.
Please eat, Regimental Commander.
- Oh, yes. Let's dig in. - Yes, sir.
JAPCHAE: SQUEEZE WATER FROM SPINACH, ADD SALT AND SESAME OIL AND TOSS
SOAK GLASS NOODLES IN WATER, CUT THE ONION INTO BITE-SIZED PIECES
Darn it.
I feel like I need to find the solution before I can start over.
- Let's serve dessert. - Yes.
This feels more like a wake than a feast.
- May I ask you something? - Yes, what is it?
When you make a dish that isn't satisfactory
How do you find a way forward?
Until I can serve a dish that makes them pick up their utensils again
I'd just keep cooking.
On and on.
This dish is how they're going to remember you, right?
- Darn it, what is he doing? - Just leave him be.
- Let's see what he's got. - Yes, understood.
Japchae. Four stars.
Add a special ingredient to upgrade the dish's class.
WILD PINE MUSHROOMS, GRADE S FROM ULJIN, GYEONGBUK
Wild pine mushrooms. Grade S.
So Grade S ingredients really do exist.
Its aroma is so intense
It fills your mouth with flavor even without any special preparation.
Who would take a knife to wild pine mushrooms?
You have to tear it along the grain to keep the aroma intact.
Oh, I see.
I didn't know that. Thank you.
WILD PINE MUSHROOM JAPCHAE
Wild pine mushroom japchae.
By adding a Grade S ingredient, one star is added.
GUILTY OF BEING TOO DELICIOUS
All right. Thanks to Corporal Lee Ho-yeong
From the appetizer to the dessert, we've enjoyed a full-course meal.
We should have promotions more often.
So we can eat lavish dishes like this.
If I had my way
I almost wish Corporal Lee Ho-yeong's discharge date would never come.
If you were to eat delicious food like this on the outside
- how much would you have to pay? - That's right.
What?
- I'm sorry I'm late. - Come to think of it
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae's dish is finally being served.
Isn't this japchae?
Yes. It's japchae made with wild pine mushrooms.
Can't you see
That we've already finished our meal, dessert and all?
No, let's at least hear his reason for making it.
Of all the possible dishes, why did you choose japchae?
I chose it because
It's an essential dish for a feast like this one.
Well, you're not wrong, but since it's japchae
I have to admit I'm not really looking forward to it.
We should have discussed the menu. I'm sorry, sir.
Gosh, but the aroma of the pine mushrooms is quite wonderful.
Order in the court.
Your Honor, the defendant armed itself with its aroma
And bewitched the people.
Objection.
The defendant couldn't help its own inherent aroma.
Overruled. Continue, prosecutor.
Furthermore, by simultaneously expressing
Both chewy and crunchy textures, it has gotten people addicted
And made it impossible for them to stop.
Leading the witness.
The people ate it of their own free will.
Your Honor, on the charge of utterly captivating people's minds
I indict the defendant, pine mushroom japchae.
THE DEFENDANT
THE JUDGE
I will now pass sentence.
The defendant, japchae.
The defendant, japchae, is guilty.
Guilty of being too delicious.
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae is guilty!
- What? - Oh, no.
This is absolutely excellent.
So the good morale in the 4th Company lately
- was all thanks to the food. - That's right.
Gosh, your skills have improved quite a bit
Since that braised boneless pollack.
Thank you, sir. Maybe because this is the Officers' Mess
It was possible because of the great ingredients
Like the pine mushrooms.
Precious pine mushrooms?
Of course
The aroma of the pine mushrooms played a big part in the japchae
But the spinach, onions, and carrots
Were of much better quality in the Officers' Mess.
Are you saying ingredients to the Officers' Mess
And the Mess Hall are different?
Support Section Chief, what is going on here?
Well...
It seems there was some kind of mistake.
As far as I know, of all the provisions that come into the Mess Hall
There haven't been any problems with any of them.
The difference in the food ingredients
Is a fact.
Outpost Commander.
Are you sure you know what you're talking about?
Since we just signed a provisions contract with a new company
It's possible that
The previous supplier intentionally delivered poor-quality provisions.
But I was never informed of anything.
Actually, this isn't something that just started happening...
I'm sorry.
We should investigate this further and then report back.
I apologize.
Let's not mess around when it comes to food.
Battalion Commander, investigate this thoroughly
- and report back to me. Understood? - Yes, sir.
Hero.
You have completed the Five-Star Quest.
As a reward, you have acquired dessert and other cooking recipes.
Thank you.
Thanks to you, I was able to finish the dish I wanted to make.
It doesn't seem like you've formally studied cooking.
I first started cooking after I joined the army.
Anyone could tell. You looked a bit clumsy and awkward.
I thought I'd improved a lot since I started
But after coming to the Officers' Mess
I truly feel like I was a frog in a well.
There are so many amazing cooks here.
I didn't expect you to suddenly serve japchae.
In a way, I guess you could call it bold.
- Thank you. - That wasn't a compliment.
Even so, I've really learned a lot today.
Could you bring me some of the japchae you made earlier?
Doesn't he usually avoid eating food made by others?
He does. He hates ruining his palate.
What do you think?
You seemed so unsure of yourself, so I was worried.
But it's better than I expected.
Thank you.
Well, but...
If it's not too much to ask
May I also try the dish you made?
- Try it. - Thank you.
I don't think I've ever had a dish that looks like this.
It's a French dish called duck confit.
France, the land of gourmet food.
The moment I take a bite
I feel like I'm in the place that every chef dreams of.
My mouth is filled.
"This is French cuisine!" It feels like it's shouting that.
Duck confit, six stars.
DUCK CONFIT IT'S ENTRANCING AND BEAUTIFUL...
It's so delicious. It's absolutely divine.
Why are you being so nice to that guy?
Don't you guys learn anything from watching him?
We can make japchae with our eyes closed.
You guys, who cook complacently, thinking "This is good enough"?
I'm sorry.
The Outpost Commander brought up something she didn't have to.
Seok-ho.
- Yes, Battalion Commander. - It's not confirmed yet
But when I get promoted and transferred to headquarters
I'm thinking of having you by my side.
Are you serious, sir?
It's more important for me to work with people I can trust.
I see.
I had no idea you thought so highly of me, Battalion Commander.
Well, you always seem so disappointed.
Anyway, I'm planning on taking you with me, all right?
Yes, sir. I understand completely.
Good.
You should start looking out for yourself now, shouldn't you?
From now on, I'll take good care of you so you won't feel left out.
Don't worry.
70TH ANNIVERSARY OF THE ARMY FOUNDING
IM SEUNG-BIN
I thought I had received a skill that was too good for me
But there are so many people far more talented than me.
And I've become curious about the path ahead of me
And just how endlessly it stretches on.
How can I...
Learn even more?
I apologize.
You shouldn't have done something you'd need to apologize for.
Right?
Yes, sir.
They told you to do a thorough comprehensive inspection
- so do it right. - I will handle it properly.
Min-gu.
You get what I'm saying, right?
Yes.
Starting with Ganglim Outpost
I will proceed.
BATTALION COMMANDER'S OFFICE
60TH REGIMENT, 1ST BATTALION GANGLIM
Before roll call next Tuesday
You are scheduled to watch an educational program
On soldiers' human rights.
- Sir, Company Commander. - What is it? We're in a meeting.
Well...
I think you need to go to the mess hall right now.
Here you go.
- Let's hurry up and get some rest. - Yes, sir.
All right, freeze!
INSPECTION
What? Salute!
As of this moment
I'm conducting a comprehensive inspection of Ganglim Outpost.
Nice to see you. Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
We keep running into each other, don't we?
THE LEGEND OF KITCHEN SOLDIER
We will now conduct an inspection of all personnel
At Ganglim Outpost.
You are here to be investigated.
Then stop trying to railroad us
And please conduct a proper investigation.
What if I go and ask the Regimental Commander myself?
Are you confident?
Hey, this has to be the church the Regimental Commander
- comes to every Sunday, right? - I made this to give to your daughter.
Are you here, So-yul?
If we give up now, the Outpost Commander will...
How can you do this so suddenly?
I'm thinking this might be a good chance to clean up Ganglim.